[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "And what happened next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, we were on the road.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "So you could see possible life at the end of the tunnel, couldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Do you still have any cognitive problems?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Yes, my wife still has problems with me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "How important looking back do you think it is to have a spouse who's just absolutely there for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "EX", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Piers, there's no -- there's no proof, you know, scientifically or medically that having a family around you in moments like that step up your recovery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NASA"]}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Have you been able to talk to any of Gabby Giffords' family throughout this process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "I've spoken to -- I've spoken to Mark, you know, her husband, who's been a remarkable astronaut, and I've covered that as well at NASA.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gabby Giffords"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "What do you -- what do you say to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "You know, in some ways, Piers, I don't really -- I don't really know what to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "You mean good news or bad news?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "You know what, good and bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Do you think you're a better reporter in a strange way for what you've been through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "You know, some people have actually said that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Did you see yourself at all in any of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Well, I -- when I was going up, I knew my body was back there, like I caught a glimpse of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Mm-hmm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Attached to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Like did you feel attached to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Do you believe it was a religious thing or -- well, what was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", ":", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "You know, this is -- this is one of those things that we will know the absolute truth of what it is that we saw and what we lived through, you know, when we die.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Now is there a delay between the table?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "But is it true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I said foxiest bikini model but you couldn't put that in the prompter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Do you seek outrage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Because it's fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Do you have any filter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Have you seen one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "It's not obviously identifiable, I have to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 338, "question": "You mean the Tea Party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "The Tea Party --", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Where's my light?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "And cancelled.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Filter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "No filter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Daughters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Not with the Bachmanns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "What can I not tell you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "You're an American citizen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "What do you think, in all seriousness, about what's happening to your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Well, I think that when I perform on the road I always thank the audience for buying a ticket because it's a big deal to buy a ticket for a live entertainment, get a baby-sitter and pay for the meal, the parking, whatever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Do you think -- do you think Washington politicians have any real connect now to the American public?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "How do you make a deal with people who don't want to make a deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Yes, he brought the stimulus package that clearly hasn't been working.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "My views about politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Honey, if I -- well, how good is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "You are, you're a businesswoman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Why are you shy about being serious about the economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Because I don't think --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Why do you find it so absurd that I would ask you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "I actually do a lot of political humor, I do more now probably than I ever have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Because you know, these politicians, they have quotes, they're the gift that keeps on giving.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Would you want to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I think it'd be fun, it'd be newsworthy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Which was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "You want to get Anderson fired.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Do you worry about being taken seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "What are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "I'm going to climb over the table.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "What is happening here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "That's called a commercial bumper.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Are we going to be de-robing as the show goes on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I have no issue with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Do you dream wistfully of being fired in totally (INAUDIBLE) and disgrace one day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "RB", ":", "NNP", ":", "CC", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Becoming unemployable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Why if you love it so much is it not on air anymore?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Well, I think because -- you know, when I started doing my show, reality was in a really different place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Why can't -- why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", ":", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Just try and control yourself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "That's the best adjective you can come up with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Well, the Twitter-sphere is going rather crazy about your performance so far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Martin"]}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "All right, who else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Steve Martin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Is he as fun at a private dinner party as I would hope he is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Did you -- did you give him a lap dance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Bit of a brazen hussy, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "What did Jack Nicholson think would be a terrible social network moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "First of all, like he knows who you are.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Nicholson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Doesn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Did he talk about me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "Not once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Hold on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "Do you watch HLN, because they're getting better numbers than you at this point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Actually, they've luckily gone back since the trial ended.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Did you cover Casey Anthony?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "A little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey Anthony"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "Where are the twins?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "I think she's a force for good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "How old is she now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "Ninety one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "And you're admitting it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "What town are you from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "I'm from Offuly (ph), is where my family eventually ended up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dublin"]}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Fact check, is there a fact check department?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "It's a place called Banahurn Offuly (ph), which is about an hour from Dublin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 753, "question": "Do you feel Irish?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "I do when I watch \"My Big Fat Gypsy Wedding.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 765, "question": "How can we top this conversation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 766, "answer": "We can beat this because we're going to talk about your plastic surgery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "What about yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "I haven't had any.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "You want to go down the list?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "Yes, please.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "Did it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 803, "question": "How much have you spent in total on resculpting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 804, "answer": "Probably -- this is so sick, but the first time I had it all done, I did like a trade out which is really one of my best whore moments ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "``", "NNS", "NNP", "''", "CC", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 809, "question": "ORGAN: What do you mean a trade out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 810, "answer": "What I mean is I went to a doctor who said, OK, if \"People Magazine\" and \"Entertainment Tonight\" cover it, I'll comp it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer Anniston"]}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 816, "question": "What did you hope would happen to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 817, "answer": "I was supposed to be Jennifer Anniston.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "What went wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "It's just -- it just doesn't really do anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 833, "question": "Did you go to Dr. Robert Maloney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 834, "answer": "I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Robert Maloney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 860, "question": "Do you like being engaged in Twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "I love Twitter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 862, "question": "How do you deal with the fury that you get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 863, "answer": "Oh, I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "Do you like the engagement on Twitter with people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "No, I like that you don't engage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 887, "question": "You mean, people @KathyGriffin and @PiersMorgan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ":", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 888, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 902, "question": "Does she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 903, "answer": "Yes, she's a good one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 904, "question": "Can you get her to Tweet me in the middle of the night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 905, "answer": "No, you're not big enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 944, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 945, "answer": "Every night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 957, "question": "Are we done now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 958, "answer": "You are done for about two minutes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 974, "question": "You mean my botched laser surgery?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 975, "answer": "I love that you made a deal with a doctor for plastic surgery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 981, "question": "Did you have to mention the doctor's name in interviews?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 982, "answer": "Yeah, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1017, "question": "How does this work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1018, "answer": "You're still live on air.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1019, "question": "What are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 1020, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ":"], "qSentId": 1033, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1034, "answer": "Oh, you did not -- I'll throw this mike pack at your --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 1040, "question": "How many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1041, "answer": "I've never counted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1042, "question": "Like how many guys have I slept with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1043, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1044, "question": "How many digits would make you happy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1045, "answer": "As many as are truthful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1051, "question": "If you could be trapped on a desert island for the rest of your life, right now, with one of your exes, who would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1052, "answer": "You.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 1063, "question": "Are you single at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1064, "answer": "I'm single, but I'm dating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1065, "question": "Who are you dating?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 1066, "answer": "Guys that ask me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 1067, "question": "Any in particular?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1068, "answer": "The ones who I happen to be home when they call.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1075, "question": "It's a nightmare, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1076, "answer": "Seriously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1077, "question": "How do they go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1078, "answer": "Well, I'm super-excited when a guy picks up the tab and has a job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1087, "question": "Are you or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1088, "answer": "I'm happy for a good lay and a pizza and a smile.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 1091, "question": "Would you like to get married again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1092, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 1093, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1094, "answer": "Did that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 1099, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1100, "answer": "I have a special needs child.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 1106, "question": "How do you see your life panning out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 1107, "answer": "Well, after this, it's in the crapper because of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1108, "question": "No, I love to do what -- it was fun when you had that show on CNN, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1109, "answer": "Loved it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1119, "question": "Now do you go to the Emmy's or are you too high and mighty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1120, "answer": "No, I went to the Emmy's last year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1124, "question": "Who is doing your dress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1125, "answer": "I haven't decided yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 1133, "question": "Didn't I see you standing outside one of the pre-Emmy parties last time trying to meet people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1134, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 1136, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1137, "answer": "I'm the greeter at the --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1151, "question": "RIFFIN: Did you enjoy it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1152, "answer": "Yes, it was funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1164, "question": "Why am I now really nervous about the last five minutes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1165, "answer": "Because you're going to check your Twitter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1180, "question": "Friend of yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1181, "answer": "Old pal of mine, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 1182, "question": "Rival?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1183, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1188, "question": "If you had to choose a one-liner to be your last line on Earth, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1189, "answer": "RIFFIN: Suck it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1200, "question": "Would you like me to help you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1201, "answer": "You can do it tonight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 1202, "question": "Would you like to do the tease to Anderson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1203, "answer": "I insist.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}}]